A Finding Aid to the Audrey Flack Papers, 1950-2009, in the Archives of American Art AAA.flacaudr
Archives of American Art
Audrey Flack papers
1950-2009
AAA.flacaudr
Archives of American Art
15.4 Linear feet
The papers of painter Audrey Flack measure 15.4 linear feet and date from 1950-2009. The collection documents Flack's career as an artist through biographical material, correspondence, extensive project files, writings and notes by Flack and others, exhibition catalogs, news and magazine clippings, other printed material, and scrapbooks. Also found are photographs by Audrey Flack as well as photographs of the artist and works of art.
Flack, Audrey
Arrangement note
The collection is arranged as 8 series.
Series 1: Biographical Material, 1951-2006 (Box 1; 0.25 linear feet)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1950-2009 (Boxes 1-3; 2.4 linear feet)
Series 3: Interviews, circa 1970-1998 (Boxes 3-4; 0.8 linear feet)
Series 4: Writings and Notes, circa 1970-2007 (Boxes 4-6; 2.15 linear feet)
Series 5: Project Files, 1966-circa 2007 (Boxes 6-11; 5.2 linear feet)
Series 6: Printed Material, 1950-2008 (Boxes 11-16, OV 17; 4.1 linear feet)
Series 7: Scrapbooks, 1977-2008 (Box 15; 2 folders)
Series 8: Photographs, 1966-2009 (Boxes 15-16; 0.5 linear feet)
Scope and Contents note
The papers of painter Audrey Flack measure 15.4 linear feet and date from 1950-2009. The collection documents Flack's career as an artist through biographical material, correspondence, extensive project files, writings and notes by Flack and others, exhibition catalogs, news and magazine clippings, other printed material, and scrapbooks. Also found are photographs by Audrey Flack as well as photographs of the artist and works of art.
Biographical material includes curricula vitae, diplomas, an award certificate, and bibliographies of monographs and articles by and about Audrey Flack. Flack's correspondence documents her professional activities and business dealings. There is correspondence with galleries, museums, arts organizations; architects and foundries; and academic institutions. Included are letters from Arizona State University, Atlantic Center for the Arts, Cooper Union, Guild Hall, Louis K. Meisel Gallery, and the Museum of Modern Art. There are letters from art historians and critics, including Flack's correspondence with Anthony Janson. Letters from publishers and agents pertain to book projects, proposals for articles, and requests to reproduce artwork in monographs or catalogs.
Interviews are recorded on four videocassettes and eight sound cassettes. Writings and notes include manuscript versions for a book, typescripts of speeches, and a notebook. Also found are audio and video recordings of lectures and talks by Flack discussing her paintings and sculptures. The collection includes extensive project files on Flack's commissioned public works and exhibitions. The files also include correspondence concerning book projects, permission requests, and Flack's participation in art educational programs.
Printed material consists of catalogs of Flack's shows, invitations and announcements to openings, press releases, reproductions of artwork, exhibition posters, clippings, periodicals, and books reflecting Flack's professional activities from the 1950s-2008. Photographs are of portraits by Flack, Flack by herself and with colleagues and students, as well as of the artist's studio. Also found are photographs of artwork.
Biographical/Historical note
Audrey Flack (1931-) is a painter and sculptor in New York City and in Long Island, New York. She earned a Bachelor of Arts from Cooper Union in 1951 and received a Bachelor of Fine Arts from Yale University in 1952. In the 1950s, she was part of the New York School that included the Abstract Expressionist painters Franz Kline and Jackson Pollock. By the 1960s, Flack had turned to painting in a realistic manner. She pioneered the technique of incorporating photographic images from contemporary sources such as magazines and newspapers; the art form became known as Photorealism. Her subjects have included families, celebrities, and public figures. An early work, The Kennedy Motorcade captured President John Kennedy moments before he was assassinated. Flack's paintings have also centered on the varied experiences of women as depicted in her Vanitas series done in the 1970s. Flack was the first Photorealist painter to have a work acquired by the Museum of Modern Art. By the 1980s, Flack was creating sculptures, goddess figures and other mythological deities of various cultures. The sculptures, many of monumental proportions were executed as commissioned works for public spaces. Flack's commissions have included Civitas: Four Visions, South Carolina, Galatea Fountain, South Pasadena, Florida, Islandia, New York City Technical College, and The Art Muse, Tampa, Florida. Further, Audrey Flack has also worked in other media such as photography and printmaking.
Audrey Flack has taught and lectured at colleges and universities in the United States and abroad, including Cooper Union, Pratt Institute of New York, and the Studio Art School International, Florence, Italy. She has been a Visiting Professor at a number of universities, including the University of North Dakota, University of Tennessee, and the University of Pennsylvania. Her paintings, watercolors, and sculptures have been featured in solo and group exhibitions in major museums and galleries. Flack's artwork has also been shown in a number of traveling exhibitions including "Saints and Other Angels: The Religious Paintings of Audrey Flack" sponsored by Cooper Union and "Breaking the Rules: Audrey Flack, A Retrospective, 1950-1990" organized by the J.B. Speed Museum. Flack has been represented by the Louis K. Meisel Gallery, the Vered Gallery, and the Gary Snyder Gallery. Among the many awards and honors she has received are the Honorary Ziegfeld Award, National Art Education Association, an Honorary Doctorate, Lyme Academy of Art, and the U.S. Government National Design for Transportation Award. Audrey Flack has also written two books and numerous articles. Audrey Flack lives and works in New York and in East Hampton, New York.
Conditions Governing Access note
Use of original material requires an appointment. Use of archival audiovisual recordings with no duplicate access copy requires advance notice.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The collection was donated by Audrey Flack in April 2009.
Related Archival Materials note
Also found in the Archives of American Art is an oral history interview with Audrey Flack conducted by Robert C. Morgan, February 16, 2009.
Arizona State University.; Atlantic Center for the Arts. (New Smyrna Beach, Fla.); Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art.; Guild Hall of East Hampton.; Janson, Anthony F.; Louis K. Meisel Gallery.; Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.).; Art--Economic aspects; Art--Study and teaching; Artists' studios--Photographs; Motion pictures (visual works); Photographs; Scrapbooks; Sound recordings; Video recordings; Women painters--New York (State)--New York; Women sculptors--New York (State)--New York
- Biographical Material, 1951-2006; Series 1; 0.25 Linear feet Box 1
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes curricula vitae, diplomas, bibliographies of monographs and articles by and about Audrey Flack. Included are abbreviated biographical accounts and the artist's philosophical statement on her work. Found is a Merit Award from the U.S. Department of Transportation presented to Flack for her design of Civitas: Four Visions.
  - Curriculum Vitae, 1990-2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Diplomas, 2001; 1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bibliographies, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Merit Award from U.S. Department of Transportation, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1950-2009; Series 2; 2.4 Linear feet Boxes 1-3
  Correspondence is mainly of a professional nature and consists of letters, e-mails, drafts, telegrams/mailgrams, and postcards. Much of the correspondence relates to the scheduling of exhibitions, loans, sales, and donations of artwork. Many letters include attachments, e.g., loan forms, consignment agreements, contracts, invoices and receipts, sales reports, sketches, printed material, photographs and slides. Correspondents include the Atlantic Center for the Arts, Cooper Union, Guild Hall, Louis K. Meisel Gallery, Museum of Modern Art, Philadelphia Museum of Art, Sidney Janis Gallery, and the Terra Museum of Art, among others.
  Flack's correspondence includes requests from academic institutions and arts organizations to teach and lecture, as well as letters from students seeking information about Flack's work. Correspondence from book publishers and university presses may include artists' questionnaires, contracts, invoices, and permission forms. Included are letters from critics, e.g., Arthur Danto and the New York Times. Flack's correspondence with art historian, Anthony Janson is of a professional and personal nature.
  Notable correspondents include Jimmy and Rosalynn Carter, Agnes Gund, Joan Mondale, and Tom Wolfe. Also found is a brief exchange of letters between Flack and Anwar Sadat relating to Flack's portrait of Sadat that was reproduced on the cover of Time Magazine. There are single letters from Judy Chicago, Willem de Kooning, and William Lieberman.
  Arrangement note
  Letters have been arranged in chronological order.
  - Undated Correspondence, circa 1950-2009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Bills and Brochures, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - Invoices and Printed Material, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - Invoices and Printed Material, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
  - Correspondence - Writings and Notes, Invoices, and Printed Material, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence - Printed Material, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8-10)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
  - Correspondence - Letters from Tom Wolfe, 1993-2007 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
  - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Interviews, circa 1970-1998; Series 3; 0.8 Linear feet Boxes 3-4
  This series includes interviews with Audrey Flack discussing her work. Included is a transcript of an interview with Audrey Flack on "The New Civic Art" conducted by David R. Brigham. Other interviews are recorded on four videocassettes and eight sound cassettes.
  Interviews have been arranged in chronological order.
  - Talk, Audrey Flack, undated; 2 Videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Audrey Flack Interviews with Cindy Nemser and "The Sunday Magazine", circa 1970; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Audrey Flack Interviews, circa 1970-circa 1980; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Interview with Audrey Flack, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Book Signing Interview, Hot Springs, Arkansas, 1991; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Audrey Flack, The Greenroom, 1992; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Transcript, "The New Civic Art, "An Interview with Audrey Flack", 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Talk, Audrey Flack, University of Louisville, 1993; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Audrey Flack with John Noonan, 1998; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Interview with Audrey Flack, The Ken Hamblin Show, 1998; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Writings and Notes, circa 1970-2007; Series 4; 2.15 Linear feet Boxes 4-6
  Writings and notes by Audrey Flack include artist's statements, drafts of a manuscript, and essays, including an account of her early years as a Photorealist artist. Included are typescripts and notes of Flack's speeches on public sculpture and her commencement address at the Boston Museum School of Fine Arts. A notebook contains Flack's notes on the creative process. Also included is an abbreviated autobiographical account.
  Writings and notes by others include masters theses and doctoral dissertations on Audrey Flack's work. Found are several poems dedicated to Audrey Flack. The files also include scattered notes by Audrey Flack, printed material, and a book proposal. Seventeen sound cassettes record Flack's talks at museums, academic institutions, and arts organizations, including Cooper Union, Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York Studio School. Fourteen videocassettes preserve her talks and panel discussions for Artists Alliance, Artists Talk on Art, St. John's Museum of Art, and other venues. Some of the sound cassettes and videocassettes are unidentified.
  This series is arranged as three subseries.
  4.1: Writings and Notes by Audrey Flack, circa 1970-2000
  4.2: Writings by Others, 1970-2007
  4.3: Lectures and Talks, 1976-2003
  - Writings and Notes by Audrey Flack, circa 1970-2000; 4.1
    - Book, circa 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Book, Second Set, circa 1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Book, Duplicates, circa 1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - My Early Years, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Speeches, circa 1970-2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Notebook, circa 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Guestbook, "Breaking the Rules: Audrey Flack, A Retrospective" (1992 September 29-December 17) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Writings and Notes by Others, 1970-2007; 4.2 (Box 4, Folder 12-15)
    - By Others, 1970-2007 (Box 4, Folder 12-15)
  - Talks and Lectures, 1976-2003; 4.3
    - Talk, "My Studio School", 1976; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Talk, Crivelli and Audrey Flack, 1977; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Panel Discussion, "Current State of Realism", circa 1980; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Panel Discussion, School of Visual Arts, circa 1980; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Flack Talks at Reynolds House, 1980; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Lecture at the University of South Florida, 1981; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) Original (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Lecture at the State University of New York, Plattsburgh, 1983; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Talk, Audrey Flack's Portraits, 1984; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Lecture, Metropolitan Museum and Long Island Art Teachers Association, 1985; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Panel Discussion, Cooper Union, New York (1986 November 4), 1 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Talk, "Artist Speaks", 1989; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Talk, American Art Forum, "Art Promotion", 1989; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Talk, Artists Alliance, circa 1990; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Talk, Audrey Flack at Guild Hall, circa 1990; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Talk, "Humanist Tradition in Painting, A Woman in the Arts", circa 1990; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Panel Discussion, "Tradition: Who Names It, Who Claims It?", circa 1990; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Panel Discussion, White Light Gallery, circa 1990; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Panel Discussion, "What Are Artists Doing With Their Lives", 1990; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Panel Discussion, "Sex, Love, and Romance," Art Show at the Vered Gallery, 1991; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) Includes written summary of program and speakers (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Lecture and Interview, Wright Art Museum, University of California, Los Angeles, 1992; 1 Sound cassettes; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Goddess Lecture, Women's Caucus for Art, 1992; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Talk, Audrey Flack at the State University of Stony Brook, 1993; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Audrey Flack Talk in Conjunction with Exhibition at the Borowsky Gallery, 1993; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Lecture, Cleveland Museum, 1995; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Talk, Sunday Today in New York, 1997; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Lecture, Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1998; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Robin C. Morgan's Dialogue with Audrey Flack at Artists Talk on Art, 1998; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) Includes letter from Robin C. Morgan (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Panel Discussion, "Art the Recording Angel: From Tragedy to Transformation" by Audrey Flack, St. John's Museum of Art, 2001; 2 Videocassettes (VHS) Duplicates (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Talk at Middle Tennessee State University, 2003; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Project Files, 1966-circa 2007; Series 5; 5.2 Linear feet Boxes 6-11
  This series primarily includes files on Audrey Flack's public works and on exhibitions. Files documenting Flack's commissioned works chart the various stages of the project. Included are letters between Flack and public officials, foundries, architects, and colleagues as well as artist's statements, informational sheets, sketches and architectural renderings, contracts, invoices, and agreements, schedules of completion, insurance forms and certificates, legal filings, printed material, and photographs. Substantive documentation is found on major commissions, including Civitas, Rock Hill, South Carolina, Queen Catherine, Queens, New York, and Veritas, Tampa, Florida.
  Exhibition-related files contain curricula vitae, correspondence, business-related materials, lists of artwork, exhibition schedules, photographs, and slides. Among the printed materials are news clippings including interviews with Flack, coverage of openings, and reviews of her work. Included are files on a major travelling exhibition "Breaking the Rules: Audrey Flack, A Retrospective, 1950-1990" organized by the J.B. Speed Art Museum that include annotated drafts of an essay by Lowery Sims written for the catalog. Two film reels document an exhibition at the Louis K. Meisel Gallery. Flack's commissions and exhibitions are recorded on eighteen videocassettes, four sound cassettes, two sound tape reels, one electronic disc (DVD), and two film reels of an unidentified project. Also included is an electronic disc (CD) in the miscellaneous project files.
  Included are files pertaining to Flack's teaching appointments, speaking engagements, and her activities in arts organizations. Interspersed among the files are typescripts on Flack's artwork and printed material, including news and magazine clippings.
  Files are arranged in alphabetical order; items within folder are arranged in rough chronological order. Researchers should also note that correspondence relating to exhibitions and commissioned pieces can be found in Series 2: Correspondence.
  - Alloway, Lawrence, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - "Art and Soul," Gauden House Studio, circa 1990; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - "The Art of the Classical Watercolor", 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Art Museum of Western Virginia, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Athens Square Park, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Atlantic Center for the Arts, 1985-1988; Includes 2 sound cassettes. (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  - Beloved Woman of Justice, Knoxville, Tennessee Courthouse, 1993-2003 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
  - Beloved Woman of Justice, Knoxville, Tennessee Courthouse, 1993-2003 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Bellonia Apollonia/The Art Muse Sculpture, 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
  - Center for Creative Imagery, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Daphne Opening (1996 July), 1 Videocassettes (Hi8) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Eastern Montana College (1982 February 9), 1 Videocassettes (Betamax) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition, "Breaking the Rules: Audrey Flack: A Retrospective, 1950-1990", 1986-1992 (Box 7, Folder 7-8)
  - Exhibition at Louis K. Meisel Gallery, circa 1988; 2 sound tape reels; 1 Videocassettes (Hi8) Super 8 mm (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
  - Flack, Audrey, Guild Hall Show (1996 July 25), 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Flack, Audrey, "Breaking the Rules for 40 Years", circa 2000; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Galatea Sculpture, City of South Pasadena, Florida, 1995-2003 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - "Hot Springs, City of the Arts in the Making," (1991 April), 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Invitations to Speak, 1972-1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Islandia Sculpture, New York City Technical College, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Lebanon Valley College, 1966-1997 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Lectures and Teaching Assignments, 1966-1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Media/Images, circa 1970-1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Missy Foundry, 1996; 1 Videocassettes (Hi8) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Nashville Symphony Association, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Nashville Symphony Association, Barbara Hoffman, Legal Bills, 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - National Museum of Women in the Arts, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - National Museum of Women in the Arts, "Four Short Pieces", 1992; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Nuell, Lon, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Oracle Sculpture, Sarasota County Selby Library, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
  - Panels, 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Panels and Lectures, Papers Written By Others and Letters, circa 1986-1991 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Public Art Sculptures, Contracts, 1992-2004 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Queen Catherine Sculpture, Queens, New York
    - Queen Catherine Sculpture, 1992-2004 (Box 8, Folder 18-20)
    - Queen Catherine Sculpture, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 1-11)
    - A.R.T. Letter, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Letters and Charlotte Klein Proposals, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Contracts and Legal Letters, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Friends of Queen Catherine, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Foundry Quotes, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Prices and Schedule, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Tallix, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Crown and Template for Jewels, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Xeroxes of Models, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Sketches, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Base Drawings, Enlargement Drawings, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Controversy, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Attacks and Audrey Flack's Letters, 1992-2004 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Legal Files, 1991-2001 (Box 10, Folder 2-9)